Preliminary Guide to the Hoof 'n' Horn Records, 1941-2019 UA.31.07.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Hoof 'n' Horn records
1941 - 2019
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Hoof 'n' Horn
UA.31.07.0002
30 Linear Feet
Hoof 'n' Horn Student Musical Theater Company was first formed in 1936 at Duke University. The organization's purpose is to provide the highest possible standard of amateur theater to the Duke University and Triangle Area communities, to serve as an educational vehicle to provide practical experience in all aspects of musical theater, and to be responsible for all necessary assets for the production of shows which it sponsors. The collection features musical scores, orchestrations, sheet music, scripts, programs, posters, a scrapbook, video and audio recordings, and administrative materials. Major subjects include Duke University students and musical productions. English.
Provenance
The Hoof 'n' Horn Records was received by the University Archives as transfers and gifts in 1977-2011, 2014, 2018, 2021, and 2022.
Historical Note
Hoof 'n' Horn Student Musical Theater Company was formed in 1936 at Duke University. Its first annual production was "Say When," performed in Page Auditorium in May 1941. The organization's purpose is to provide the highest possible standard of amateur theater to the Duke University and Triangle Area communities, to serve as an educational vehicle to provide practical experience in all aspects of musical theater, and to be responsible for all necessary assets for the production of shows which it sponsors.
Collection Overview
The collection features musical scores, orchestrations, sheet music, scripts, programs, posters, a scrapbook, video and audio recordings, and administrative materials. Materials range in date from 1941 to 2019.
Related Material
University Archives Poster Collection, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Conditions Governing Access
Access note. Some materials in this collection are fragile audiovisual materials that may need to be reformatted before use. Contact Research Services for access.
Posters; Scores; Scrapbooks; Scripts (documents); Sheet music; Sound recordings; Video recordings; Theater programs; Musical theater; Musicals; Musicals -- Production and direction; Musicals -- Writing and publishing; Musicals -- Video recordings; Playbills; Duke University. Hoof 'n' Horn; Duke University -- Students
- Container List
  - Student Written Scripts (Box 1)
    - An Evening With Sigmund Freud, 1959 (Box 1)
    - Ring Around the Moon (Box 1)
    - Top Secret, 1956 (Box 1)
  - Scores and Orchestrations
    - Lovin' Time, 1949 (Box 1)
    - Untitled (Box 1)
    - An Evening With Sigmund Freud, 1959 (Box 1)
    - Nuthin' Like It, 1948 (Box 1)
    - Ring Around the Moon (Box 1)
    - Top Secret, 1956 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous Songs (Box 1)
    - Student Written (Box 2)
      - Say When, 1941 (Box 2)
      - Top Secret, 1956 (Box 2)
      - Laughing with You, 1955 (Box 2)
      - Nervous Norval (Box 2)
      - Flap 'Er Sails, 1950 (Box 2)
      - Belles and Ballots, 1951 (Box 2)
    - The Thirteen Clocks (Box 2)
  - Student Written Scripts
    - I'm Emir Here, 1957 (Box 2)
  - General Historical Information (Box 3)
  - Trust Fund for Fearing Children, 1955 (Box 3)
  - Equipment Trust Fund, 1948-1979 (Box 3)
  - Financial Statements, 1971-1984 (Box 3)
  - Magnolias and Madness, Student Written Script, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Playbills and Publicity (Box 3)
  - Programs
    - Another Saturday Night, 1977 (Box 3)
    - The Music Man, 1982/1983 (Box 3)
    - How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying, 1969 (Box 3)
    - Laughing With You, 1955 (Box 3)
    - Man of La Mancha, 1989/1990 (Box 3)
    - A Chorus Line, 1991/1992 (Box 3)
    - Magnolias and Madness, 1958 (Box 3)
    - Lovintime, 1949 (Box 3)
    - Belles and Ballots, 1951 (Box 3)
    - Flap 'Er Sails, 1950 (Box 3)
    - The Boy Friend, 1961 (Box 3)
    - Anything Goes, 1985/1986 (Box 3)
    - Once Upon a Mattress, 1962 (Box 3)
    - Bye Bye Birdie, 1963 (Box 3)
    - Company, 1985 (Box 3)
    - Can-Can, 1964 (Box 3)
    - Anyone Can Whistle, 1971 (Box 3)
    - Cabaret, 1972 (Box 3)
    - A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum, 1973 (Box 3)
    - Anything Goes, 1952 (Box 3)
    - Promises, Promises, 1974 (Box 3)
    - Applause, 1974/1975 (Box 3)
    - A Little Night Music, 1974/1975 (Box 3)
    - My Fair Lady, 1975/1976 (Box 3)
    - The Apple Tree, 1977/1978 (Box 3)
    - Gypsy, 1975/1976 (Box 3)
    - Camelot, 1976/1977 (Box 3)
    - No, No Nanette, 1978 (Box 3)
    - Fiddler on the Roof, 1979/1980 (Box 3)
    - Honesty (Box 3)
    - You're a Good Man, Charlie Brown, 1980/1981 (Box 3)
    - The Diary of Adam and Eve (Act I of The Apple Tree), 1977 (Box 3)
    - Grease, 1980/1981 (Box 3)
    - Little Me, 1979/1980 (Box 3)
    - Bells are Ringing, 1970 (Box 3)
    - Say When, 1941 (Box 3)
    - A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum, 1982 (Box 3)
    - Chicago, 1984 (Box 3)
    - I'm Emir Here, 1957 (Box 3)
    - Merrily We Roll Along, 1984 (Box 3)
    - She Loves Me, 1983 (Box 3)
    - The Best Little Whorehouse in Texas, 1985 (Box 3)
    - Pippin, 1979 (Box 3)
    - And If Elected, 1960 (Box 3)
    - Hullabaloo, 1951 (Box 3)
    - The Laugh's the Thing, 1942 (Box 3)
  - Reviews, etc. (Box 3)
  - News Clippings (Box 3)
  - Nuthin' Like It, Student Written Lyrics, 1948 (Box 3)
  - I'm Emir Here, Student Written Scores, 1957 (Box 3)
  - Magnolias and Madness, Student Written Score, 1958 (Box 3)
  - Scrapbook, 1950s (Box 4 (Oversize))
  - Scores and Orchestrations
    - Lovintime, 1949 (Box 4 (Oversize))
    - Flap 'Er Sails, 1950 (Box 4 (Oversize))
    - Belles and Ballots, 1951 (Box 4 (Oversize))
    - Magnolias and Madness, 1958 (Box 5 (Oversize))
    - Oversize scores and orchestrations from boxes 1 and 2 (Box 6 (Oversize))
- UA2003-0014
  - Video Recordings (Box 7)
    - UMatic 60m
      - Damn Yankees, 1989/90, [3 cassettes] (Box 7)
      - Man of La Mancha, 1989/90, [3 cassettes] (Box 7)
      - Guys & Dolls, Man of La Mancha Highlights, 1989/90 (Box 7)
      - West Side Story, October, 1990, [3 cassettes] (Box 7)
      - Cabaret, January, 1991, [3 cassettes] (Box 8)
      - Pippin, April, 1991, [v.1, 2 of ?] (Box 8)
      - A Chorus Line, 1991/1992, [3 cassettes] (Box 8)
      - Godspell, January, 1993, [3 cassettes] (Box 8)
      - Grease, April, 1993, [v.1, 2 of ?] (Box 8)
    - VHS (Box 9)
      - Baby, October, 1987 (Box 9)
      - Red Hot & Cole, 1998/99 (Box 9)
      - Godspell, 1989 (Box 9)
      - Man of La Mancha, Winter, 1990 (Box 9)
      - Assassins, October, 1992 (Box 9)
      - Moby Dick, 1993/1994 (Box 9)
      - Grease, April, 1993 (Box 9)
      - Working, 1993/94 (Box 9)
      - Little Shop of Horrors, 1995 (Box 9)
      - Best Little Whorehouse in Texas, April, 1996 (Box 9)
      - Syekul, March, 1996 (Box 9)
      - Stuck, March, 1996 (Box 9)
      - Pippin, 1997 (Box 9)
      - Baby, January, 1997 (Box 9)
      - Guys and Dolls, April, 1997 (Box 9)
      - Jesus Christ Superstar, 1997/98 (Box 9)
      - Company, 1997/1998 (Box 9)
      - Red Hot & Cole, 1998/99 (Box 9)
      - Sweet Charity, October, 1999 (Box 9)
      - The Fantasticks, January, 2000 (Box 9)
      - A Chorus Line, April, 2000 (Box 9)
      - A Funny Thing Happened… Forum, Spring 2001 (Box 9)
      - Grand Hotel, October 2001 (Box 9)
      - Godspell, January, 2002 (Box 9)
      - Kiss Me, Kate, Spring, 2002 (Box 9)
      - The Mystery of Edwin Drood, Fall 2002 (Box 9)
      - Passing the Quarter, The Company of Company: A Documentary and Outtakes (Box 9)
    - DVD
      - Urinetown, Spring 2006 (Box 9)
  - Audio Recordings (Box 10)
    - LP
      - Top Secret, 1955 (Box 10)
    - Reels
      - ADF Student Performance, 1986 (Box 10)
      - The Fantasticks, 1986/87 (Box 10)
      - Brigadoon, April, 1987
        - Act I. 2 Track Master (Box 10)
        - Act II. 2 Track Master (Box 10)
        - Cast #1. 4 Track (Box 10)
        - Cast #2. 4 Track (Box 10)
        - Cast #3. 4 Track (Box 10)
        - Sound Effects, [2 reels] (Box 10)
      - Once Upon a Mattress, 1987/88
        - Sound Effects [2 reels] (Box 10)
        - Sound Effects (Box 20)
      - Kiss Me, Kate, April, 1988 (Box 20)
        - 4 Tracks [2 reels] (Box 20)
        - Sound Effects (Box 20)
      - Sound Effects, Rain and Thunder (Box 20)
      - DeGarmo and Key, [2 Reels] (Box 11)
      - [Unknown] Act I (Box 11)
      - [Unknown] Act III (Box 11)
  - Posters (Box 12)
    Scope and Contents note
    Additional Hoof 'n' Horn posters can be found in the University Archives Poster Collection.
    - Little Shop of Horrors, 2002/2003 (Box 12)
    - Mystery of Edwin Drood, Fall 2002 (Box 12)
    - Kiss Me, Kate, Spring 2002 (Box 12)
    - Godspell, 2001/2002 (Box 12)
    - Grand Hotel, Fall 2001 (Box 12)
    - A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum, Spring 2001 (Box 12)
    - Tommy, 2000/2001 (Box 12)
    - A Chorus Line, Spring 2000 (Box 12)
    - The Fantasticks, 1999/2000 (Box 12)
    - Sweet Charity, Fall 1999 (Box 12)
    - Company, 1997/1998 (Box 12)
    - Baby, 1996/1997 (Box 12)
    - Guys and Dolls, 1996/1997 (Box 12)
    - Best Little Whorehouse in Texas, 1995/1996 (Box 12)
    - Hair, Spring 1995 (Box 12)
    - Working, 1993/1994 (Box 12)
    - Moby Dick, Fall 1993 (Box 12)
    - Godspell, 1992/1993 (Box 12)
    - Grease, 1992/1993 (Box 12)
    - The Bored Princess, 1992/1993 (Box 12)
    - A Chorus Line, 1991/1992 (Box 12)
    - The Mystery of Edwin Drood, Fall 1991 (Box 12)
    - Starting Here, Starting Now, 1991/1992 (Box 12)
    - Cabaret, 1990/1991 (Box 12)
    - Pippin, 1990/1991 (Box 12)
    - Trust Me!, 1989/1990 (Box 12)
    - Damn Yankees, 1989/1990 (Box 12)
    - Man of la Mancha, 1989/1990 (Box 12)
    - Guys and Dolls, 1989/1990 (Box 12)
    - A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum, 1988/1989 (Box 12)
    - Sweet Charity, 1988/1989 (Box 12)
    - Kiss Me, Kate, 1987/1988 (Box 12)
    - Once Upon a Mattress, 1987/1988 (Box 12)
    - Cole, 1986/1987 (Box 12)
    - The Fantasticks, 1986/1987 (Box 12)
    - Godspell, 1983/1984 (Box 12)
    - Chicago, 1983/1984 (Box 12)
    - Merrily We Roll Along, 1983/1984 (Box 12)
    - The Music Man, 1982/1983 (Box 12)
    - You're a Good Man, Charlie Brown, 1980 (Box 12)
    - Another Saturday Night, 1977 (Box 12)
    - The Apple Tree, 1977/1978 (Box 12)
    - A Little Night Music, 1974/1975 (Box 12)
    - Encore! (Box 12)
  - Executive Council (Box 13)
    - 1987-1988 (Box 13)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 13)
    - Alumni and Reunions, 1984 (Box 13)
    - Financial records
      - Box Office Reports, 1962-1984 (Box 13)
      - External Business Contracts
        - MTI, 1966-1986 (Box 13)
        - Rodgers and Hammerstein, 1970 (Box 13)
        - Tams-Witmark, 1970-1981 (Box 13)
      - Financial Statements, June 30, 1985- March 30, 1986 (Box 13)
      - Financial Statements, Final, 1968-1985 (Box 13)
      - Grease Budget, 1980
        - 1985 (Box 13)
    - Playreading Committee, 1995 (Box 13)
    - Save Our Ass Committee, Reynolds Theater Rental Concerns, 1985-1986 (Box 13)
  - General subject and correspondence files
    - Audition sheet, etc. (Box 13)
    - Costumes, 1977 (Box 13)
    - Music, Orchestration, 1979 (Box 13)
    - Set Design (Box 13)
    - Tickets, 1980-1984 (Box 13)
    - Letters Outgoing, 1985 (Box 13)
    - Letters Received, 1985 (Box 13)
  - Productions
    - Cabaret, Spring 2003 (Box 13)
    - A Chorus Line, Spring 2000 (Box 13)
    - A Funny Thing Happened On the Way to the Forum, Spring 2001 (Box 13)
    - Kiss Me, Kate, Spring 2002 (Box 13)
    - Little Shop of Horrors, Winter 2002/2003 (Box 13)
    - Mystery of Edwin Drood, Fall 2002 (Box 13)
    - Sweet Charity, 1988/1989 (Box 13)
  - Programs (Box 13)
  - Student-Written Scripts
    - I'm Emir Here, 1957 (Box 13)
    - Top Secret, 1956 (Box 13)
    - Ring Around the Moon, undated (Box 13)
    - Extra!, undated (Box 13)
  - Constitution, 1952 (Box 14)
  - Constitution and By-Laws, undated (Box 14)
  - By-Laws, 1984, 1987, undated (Box 14)
  - Spring Producer Notebook, 1999 (Box 14)
  - Spring Show Supplemental Notebook, 1999 (Box 14)
  - Fall Producer Notebook, 1999 (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Stage Manager's Handbook, circa 2001 (Box 14)
  - Winter Show Supplemental Notebook: Working, 1993-1994 (Box 14)
  - Winter Show Supplemental Notebook: Little Shop of Horrors, 1995 (Box 14)
  - Winter Show Supplemental Notebook: Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat, 1996 (Box 14)
  - Winter Show Supplemental Notebook, 1997-1999 (Box 14)
  - Winter Show Supplemental Notebook: The Fantasticks, 2000 (Box 14)
  - Winter Show Supplemental Notebook: Notebook Evolution, 2000 (Box 14)
  - Producer's Notebook: Kiss Me Kate, 2002 (3 folders) (Box 14)
  - Lists of Shows Since 1936, circa 1999-2003 (Box 14)
  - Ring Around the Moon, 1950 Fall (Box 14)
  - Kiss Me Kate, 2002 (Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous Songs, 1951, undated (Box 14)
  - Trust Me.. ., script, circa 1990 (Box 14)
  - Pippin, script, undated (Box 14)
  - The Bored Princess, script, undated (Box 14)
  - Kidpower and His Sidekick Brat, cript and sheet music, undated (Box 14)
  - Reefer Madness, script, undated (Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous Scripts, undated (Box 14)
  - Space and Property, 1974, 1991-1992 (Box 14)
  - Financial: Merrily We Roll Along, 1984 Fall (Box 14)
  - Hints for a New Makeup Chairman, 1977 (Box 14)
  - Student-Written Musical Program, 1988-1991 (Box 14)
  - Non-Show Activities, 1986-1991 (Box 14)
  - 1991-1992 Season (Box 14)
  - Costumes and Makeup, circa 1990 (Box 14)
  - Costumer, 1999, undated (Box 14)
  - The Wisdom of Kitty Passed On To Julie Foh, Student Written Producer, undated (Box 14)
  - Hymn: Onward, Hoof'n'Horners, 1995 (Box 14)
  - Programs and Playbills, 1941-1942, 1949, 1951-1953 (Box 14)
  - Programs and Playbills, 1961-1969, 1972 (Box 14)
  - Programs and Playbills, 1981-1989 (Box 14)
  - Programs and Playbills, 1990-1999 (Box 14)
  - Programs and Playbills, 2001-2002, undated (Box 14)
  - Playbills: Duke University Artists Series, 1992/1993-1998/1999 (Box 14)
  - Alumni, 1987-1990, undated (Box 14)
  - Alumni Scrapbook by Tina Bell Midgett (Class of 1951), 2001 and Duke Anedotes, compiled by Tina Bell Midgett at the Class of 1951's 50th Reunion, 2001 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Publications, 1987, 1997-1999, 2002, 2005 (Box 14)
  - Publicity, circa 1961-1997, undated (Box 14)
  - Clippings and Printed Material, circa 1941-1998, undated (Box 14)
  - Petition to Keep Independent, Student-Run Organizations, 1987 (Box 14)
  - General Business, circa 1985 (Box 14)
  - History and Purpose, circa 1987-1991 (Box 14)
  - Newsletters, 1990 Summer, undated (Box 14)
  - Meeting Minutes, 1982 April 19, April 24 (Box 14)
  - Financial Statements, 1970 (Box 14)
  - Financial: The Best Little Whorehouse in Texas, 1985 (Box 14)
  - Finances/Development, 1982-1985 (Box 14)
  - Miscellaneous, 1990s, undated (Box 14)
  - Correspondence/Memoranda, 1979-1986 (Box 14)
  - Photographs and Slides (Box 15)
    Scope and Contents
    Largely unidentified and undated, many are loose, include both color and black/white, cast shots and production shots.
  - Photograph Albums (3) (Box 15)
  - Hullabaloo, undated (Box 15)
  - Royalty Payment Receipts, 1998 (Box 15)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1999 (Box 15)
  - Duke Student Arts Group Meeting: Minutes, 1988 Dec. 7 (Box 15)
  - Financial: Kiss Me Kate, 2002 (Box 15)
  - Financial: Tommy, 2000-2001 (Box 15)
  - Finances/Development, 1986-1990 (Box 15)
  - David Ball: Artistic Director, 1985-1990 (Box 15)
  - University Relations, 1986-1991 (Box 15)
  - Theater Facilities User Committee, 1986-1991 (Box 15)
  - Student Affairs Leadership Program, 1988-1991 (Box 15)
  - Durham Arts Council, 1991 (Box 15)
  - Scrapbooks/Photograph Albums (3) (Box 16)
  - Audio-Visual Material (Box 17)
    Access Restrictions
    Use of audiotapes and videotapes from this collection requires the creation of reference copies.
    - VHS Cassette: Kiss Me Kate, 2002 (Box 17)
    - VHS Cassette: Moby Dick, undated (Box 17)
    - VHS Cassette: Working, undated (Box 17)
    - VHS Cassette: The Mystery of Edwin Drood, 2002 (Box 17)
    - VHS Cassette: Syekul and Stuck, 1996 (Box 17)
    - VHS Cassette: Into the Woods, 1994 (Box 17)
    - VHS Cassette: West Side Story, undated (Box 17)
    - VHS Cassette: The Best Little Whorehouse in Texas, 1996 April 19 (Box 17)
    - VHS Cassette: Little Shop of Horrors, 1995 (Box 17)
    - VHS Cassette: Guys and Dolls, 1997 (Box 17)
    - VHS Cassette: Damn Yankees, 1990 (Box 17)
    - VHS Cassette: Baby, 1997 (Box 17)
    - VHS Cassette: Company, undated (Box 17)
    - VHS Cassette: A Chorus Line, 2000 (Box 17)
    - VHS Cassette: Sweet Charity, 1999 (Box 17)
    - VHS Cassette: The Fantasticks, 2000 (Box 17)
    - VHS Cassette: Tommy, 2000 (Box 17)
    - Digital 8: Into the Woods, undated (Box 17)
    - DVCam: West Side Story, undated (Box 17)
    - DVCam: The Wiz, 2003 (Box 17)
    - DVD: The Pajama Game, undated (Box 17)
    - DVD: Once Upon a Mattress, 2005 (Box 17)
    - Audiocassettes: Various songs, cotents of some are unknown (9 total) (Box 17)
    - LPs (2) (Box 18)
  - Scrapbooks (3) (Box 18)
  - Rent poster, undated (Box 18)
  - All's Fair in Love poster, undated (Box 18)
  - Belles and Ballots sheet music, undated (Box 18)
- UA2012-0008
  - Another Saturday Night, 1977 (Box 19)
  - American Dream, circa 1987-1988 (2 folders) (Box 19)
  - Programs, Articles, Reviews, 1958, 1979-1981, undated (Box 19)
  - Programs, Articles, Reviews, 1979-1981 (Box 19)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 19)
- UA2014-0038
  - Working, January 1983 (Box 19)
- UA2018.0055, 1
  - Hoof 'n' Horn Publicity, 1958 April (Box 19)
  - Desire Under the Elms, undated (Box 19)
  - Richard III, undated (Box 19)
  - Guys and Dolls, 1967 April (Box 19)
  - Sweet Charity, 1968 June (Box 19)
  - Out of this World, 1965 April (Box 19)
  - Can Can, 1964 April (Box 19)
  - Tea House Under the August Moon, undated (Box 19)
  - Bye Bye Birdie, 1963 April (Box 19)
  - Once Upon a Mattress, 1962 April (Box 19)
  - Duke Players, 1961-1965 (Box 19)
  - Materials from Foamin' Over and other productions, 1950-1954 (Box 19)
  - Hoof'n'Horn constitution and Flap 'Er Sails materials, c. 1950 (Box 19)
- UA2021.0017, 1956-2019
  - Secret society scene (Box 19)
  - Assassins script (Box 19)
  - I'm Emir Here script (Box 19)
  - Top Secret script, 1956 (Box 19)
  - Duke Parents Program Co-Chair Dinner, 2017 (Box 19)
  - Chess t-shirt (Box 21)
  - A Chorus Line t-shirt, 2000 (Box 21)
  - Violet pin (Box 21)
  - The Pajama Game, DVD, 2007-2008 (Box 17, Video-disc UA31070022-DVD-0001)
- UA2021-0038, circa 2010 - 2011
  - Hoof'n'Horn presents RENT Friday, Tape 1, 2010 April 16 (Box 22, Video-cassette UA31.07.0002-MDV-0001)
  - Hoof'n'Horn presents RENT Friday, Tape 2, 2010 April 16 (Box 22, Video-cassette UA31.07.0002-MDV-0002)
  - RENT, 2010 April 16 (Box 22, Video-cassette UA31.07.0002-MDV-0003)
  - Friday Act I Opening A Very Nice Prince (no audio), circa 2010 - 2011 (Box 22, Video-cassette UA31.07.0002-MDV-0004)
  - The Frog Prince, 2011 March 27 (Box 22, Video-cassette UA31.07.0002-MDV-0005)
  - Company Saturday show 8 Tape 1, circa 2010 - 2011 (Box 22, Video-cassette UA31.07.0002-MDV-0006)
  - Company Saturday show 8 Tape 2, circa 2010 - 2011 (Box 22, Video-cassette UA31.07.0002-MDV-0007)
  - Company Saturday show 8 Tape 3, circa 2010 - 2011 (Box 22, Video-cassette UA31.07.0002-MDV-0008)
  - Chess Friday Night, 2011 February 04 (Box 22, Video-cassette UA31.07.0002-MDV-0009)
  - Chess Friday Night, 2011 February 04 (Box 22, Video-cassette UA31.07.0002-MDV-0010)
  - Chess Friday Night, 2011 February 04 (Box 22, Video-cassette UA31.07.0002-MDV-0011)
  - Chess Saturday Matinee, 2011 February 05 (Box 22, Video-cassette UA31.07.0002-MDV-0012)
  - Chess Saturday Matinee, 2011 February 05 (Box 22, Video-cassette UA31.07.0002-MDV-0013)
  - Chess, circa 2011 February (Box 22, Video-cassette UA31.07.0002-MDV-0014)
  - Chess, circa 2011 February (Box 22, Video-cassette UA31.07.0002-MDV-0015)
  - Chess, circa 2011 February (Box 22, Video-cassette UA31.07.0002-MDV-0016)
  - Aida, 2011 April 15 (Box 22, Video-cassette UA31.07.0002-MDV-0017)
  - Aida, 2011 April 15 (Box 22, Video-cassette UA31.07.0002-MDV-0018)
  - Into the Woods, circa 2010 - 2011 (Box 22, Video-cassette UA31.07.0002-MDV-0019)
  - Act I Saturday Evening Into the Woods, circa 2010 - 2011 (Box 22, Video-cassette UA31.07.0002-MDV-0020)
  - Act I continued Saturday Evening and Act II Into the Woods, circa 2010 - 2011 (Box 22, Video-cassette UA31.07.0002-MDV-0021)
  - Into the Woods Act II, circa 2010 - 2011 (Box 22, Video-cassette UA31.07.0002-MDV-0022)
  - Saturday Matinee Into the Woods, circa 2010 - 2011 (Box 22, Video-cassette UA31.07.0002-MDV-0023)
  - Saturday Matinee Into the Woods, circa 2010 - 2011 (Box 22, Video-cassette UA31.07.0002-MDV-0024)
  - Saturday Matinee Into the Woods, circa 2010 - 2011 (Box 22, Video-cassette UA31.07.0002-MDV-0025)
- UA2022-0007, 1957-1973
  Conditions Governing Access
  Access note.Some materials are fragile audiovisual formats that may need to be reformatted before use. Contact Research Services for access.
  - Programs, 1969-1973; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Executive Council papers, 1970-1973 (Box 23)
  - The Triangle Pointer, 1971-1972 (Box 23)
  - Duke University Calendar, 1972 April (Box 23)
  - Correspondence, 1973 (Box 23)
  - Publicity, undated (Box 23)
  - Stop the World I Want to Get Off poster, 1972 (Box 24)
  - A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum poster, 1973 (Box 24)
  - I'm Emir Here, 1957 (Audio-phonodisc PD 1)
  - And If Elected, 1960 (Audio-phonodisc PD 2)
- UA2022-0058, 1987
  - Cole performance CDs, 1987; 2 cdrs (Box 22, Audio-cd UA31.07.0002-CD-0001, UA31.07.0002-CD-0002)
  - Cole flash drive, 1987 (Box 22, Digital-materials UA31.07.0002-USB-0001)
    Contains photos, videos, and audio recordings of Hoof 'n' Horn's production of Cole.
  - Cole programs, 1987 (Box 23)